Metal Cardbot Commentary!
Hide Your Identity!
Hey, everyone! Jun here!
Let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Hello, everyone.
My name is Phoenix Fire!
It's nice to see all of you again, friends!
It's nice to see you again, Phoenix Fire!
Today, let's see what all the commotion was about
when Anna came over to my house!
So, shall we get started?
Hey, Dad! Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
Tell me, what day is it tomorrow? 🎵
Did you forget? I'll give you a hint, it's-
Is it our son's turn to do the chores?
No, no, it's something more special than-
Is it time for spring cleaning? Your room is getting pretty messy, after all.
I would appreciate it if you could clean the garage and mow the lawn while you're at it. Eh?
Ugh... Tch.
Jun! You mustn't leave your room a mess!
It should always be clean!
No! It's not that dirty... is it?
If your room is messy, germs and bugs can breed and spread!
Causing colds and various diseases-
Ugh. You're nagging me too much, Phoenix Fire!
Wait... Vera, do you have a crush on-
No!
I'm just keeping an eye on him. I'm going to find out his secret!
Secret?
Yes! It's something so top secret that even FBI agents would be rushing after him!
You'd better watch out!
Top secret...?
It's my birthday, so why do I have to mow the lawn?!
Both Mom and Dad aren't showing any love for their son today.
Jun, whatcha doin'?
Can't you see? I'm mowing the lawn!
It looks fun! Let me try, let me try!
Whaa?
Woohoo!
Having fun?
Haha! This is the best!
Wow!
I also want to clean the houses that the people of Earth live in!
What?
Why does everyone find cleaning so fun?
Jun, can I clean it with my water cannon using Water Splash?
Ah, no way!
If you do that, my house would get blown to bits!
What if someone sees them? We agreed to keep Metal Cardbots a secret.
That's right, but...
Hello!
H-Heyyy!
It's an emergency! Hurry, hurry, transform!
This is bad!
Sorry for dropping in like this. Is now a bad time?
Of course not! You guys are always welcome here!
I'm glad! What were you up to?
Uh... Just some yard work?
Wow! Can I see?
B-b-b-but Anna! I-It's not done yet!
Why is there a truck in your yard?
Uh, someone just asked me to take care of it!
Aah! Hey! Wait!
Why don't we-
Aah!
Shadow X, stealth mode on!
Stop that. What are you doing?
Phew~
That was a close one, Jun!
I didn't expect Anna to come over.
I understand, Jun.
If a girl you like comes to you, you can't refuse her.
Wh-what does that mean, Phoenix Fire?!
It’s not like that!
Maybe he was taken hostage by robbers!
Eh??
You came running because you thought I was taken hostage?!
Blue Cop worries about Jun too much!
What was that?
It sounded like a car accident!
Anyway, let's blow out the candles!
Yes! Let's sing Happy Birthday now!
1, 2, 3!
Happy birthday to me...
Hello.
Aah!!
Mowtown was almost completely destroyed!
Blue Cop, I'll have to make you write a 100 page essay reflecting on today!
Well, everyone?
In the end, we were caught by Anna and the Metal Cardbots' identity was revealed.
I hope you look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!